Hello, my name is Ashel Troncoso, owner of ATI Insurance Group, and I'm making this video to recommend Samuel Ochoa and his AI services.
When he approached me, I was as skeptical as could be. Honestly, I did not really want to integrate anything with AI. I really didn't trust it.
And honestly speaking, I just didn't think it was going to really work.
And after a bit of back and forth with him, he finally convinced me to give it a try. And I'm super happy that I did.
He honestly has helped me create some workflows that have saved me five minutes here, 10 minutes here with my business, whether it's helping with organization, reminders, prep work with e-signs or just other things with PDFs.
And it's been a really good thing and it's been very productive for me and my business.
I would absolutely recommend working with him as he's very patient and he really just loves what he does.
He loves teaching. He loves seeing you, you know, win and make what you need come true.
So if you're looking for someone that is going to teach you AI and really go into detail, he's your guy.
So thank you so much. And yeah, I appreciate you, Sam. Keep up the hard work.